http://www.chesapeakemedicalstaffing.com/terms-and-conditions-plus-privacy-statement/

Terms, Conditions & Privacy Statement | Chesapeake Medical Staffing
Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
TermsBy accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
DisclaimerThe materials on Chesapeake Medical Staffing’ web site are provided “as is.” Chesapeake Medical Staffing makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Chesapeake Medical Staffing does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site
LimitationsIn no event shall Chesapeake Medical Staffing be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Chesapeake Medical Staffing’s Internet site, even if Chesapeake Medical Staffing or a Chesapeake Medical Staffing authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
Revisions and ErrataThe materials appearing on Chesapeake Medical Staffing’s website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Chesapeake Medical Staffing does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Chesapeake Medical Staffing may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Chesapeake Medical Staffing does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
LinksChesapeake Medical Staffing is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Chesapeake Medical Staffing of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.
Site Terms of Use ModificationsAmerican Surgical Professionals may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
Governing LawThis site is created and controlled by Chesapeake Medical Staffing, an American Medical Staffing Network Company, in the State of Texas, USA, and the laws of the State of Texas shall govern these terms, conditions and disclaimers. Chesapeake Medical Staffing reserves the right to make changes to this site and to these terms, conditions and disclaimers at any time, without prior notice.
Chesapeake Medical Staffing, 2401 York Road, Timonium, MD 21093
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
This is the Privacy, Cookies & Data Security Policy (the “Policy”) for www.cms24-7.com (the “Site”). This Policy describes what, how and why we collect, process and store information about you. This Policy specifies your rights to access, correct, dispute or delete information about you. By accessing the Site, you expressly consent to the terms of this Policy, including our collection, processing and storage of information about you in the United States. Chesapeake Medical Staffing reserves the right to make changes to this Policy without notice.
All information about you, including information collected through the Site, is collected, processed and stored by Chesapeake Medical Staffing, 2401 York Road, Timonium, MD 21093.
Data Collection
To serve our potential employees, employees, and clients, we may request your first name, last name, email address and phone number. We may request additional information from you such as educational background, work history, curriculum vitae, specialty, preferred work location or other information which we may append to a data record.
In addition to the information you provide, the Site uses cookies to collect and store information about you and your browsing history. These typically involve pieces of information or code that the Site transmits to you and which is stored in your browser, on your computer’s hard drive or on mobile device. Our cookies track information to remember you and your browsing preferences. You may configure your browser to reject cookies but this step may result in a poor Site experience.
We use two types of cookies:
Cookies that enable you to log into the Site, if you are an employee of Chesapeake Medical Staffing.
Cookies that enable us to analyze our Site traffic. These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors, new and returning, and to understand how our visitors use the Site. This helps us for our legitimate interests of improving the way the Site works.
Disclosure of Your Data
We may disclose information about you to: (1) any member of our corporate group, which means our parent (American Surgical Professionals), or our Network Company (American Medical Staffing), which support our collection, processing, storage and use of information pursuant to this Policy; or (2) selected third parties, which may include: (a) organizations who process information on our behalf and in accordance with our instructions; (b) our clients, with the permission of our potential or existing employees.
We will disclose information about you: (1) in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, or if we (or a substantial portion of our assets) are acquired by a third party, in which case we will disclose information about our users to the prospective seller or buyer of such business assets subject to the terms of this Policy; (2) if we are under a duty to disclose or share information in order to comply with any legal obligation; (3) in order to enforce or apply the terms of this Policy or other agreements with you; or (4) to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or third parties.
Data Security
With respect to information we collect, process and store, we have implemented reasonable technical and physical security protocols to (a) ensure the security and confidentiality of the information; (b) protect against anticipated threats or hazards to the security or integrity of the information; (c) protect against unauthorized access to or use of the information; and (d) ensure the proper disposal of the information.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a username and/or password that enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this username and password confidential. We ask that you not share your username or password with anyone.
Note that the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted to the Site, and any transmission of information is at your own risk. Upon receipt of your information, we will use strict procedures and security measures to prevent unauthorized access.
Data Storage and Retention
All information is collected, processed and stored in the United States of America. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that information about you is subject to appropriate safeguards to ensure your information is secure.
We retain information about you for so long as we deem reasonably necessary. We periodically evaluate information about you for destruction in the event such information is no longer reasonably necessary to our operations.
Your Rights
You have the right to:
Request that we correct any information about you that is incorrect.
Request that we delete information about you, subject to our reasonable technical ability and subject to legal reasons which do not require us to delete information about you.
Withdraw your consent at any time to our use of information about you.
Be provided with a copy of all information about you which is held by us.
Request that information about you be moved to a third party.
If your request or concern is not satisfactorily resolved by us, you have the right to lodge a complaint with an applicable data supervisory authority.
If you believe that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, contact us immediately via email.
2401 York Road,Timonium, MD 21093 1.410.321.4267Copyright 2019 Chesapeake Medical Staffing
Type and Press “enter” to Search
